Preliminary Inventory to the Ralph James Watkins Papers, 1926-1978
Hoover Institution Archives
- Boxes 48-94
  - Taiwan (Box 68)
    - Comparative international data
    - Council for U.S. Aid
    - Working Group on Credit Control
    - Economic conditions
    - Public health
    - Questionnaires on economic and financial developments, 1960-1961
    - Railway Administration
    - Retired Servicemen Program
    - Private industry
    - Achievements of the Taiwan Provincial Administration, 1960
    - Monetary and credit policy
    - Population (Box 69)
    - National income
    - Travel - Inspection visits
    - Water resources planning
    - Land reform
    - Investments
    - Industrial developments
  - Eastern Region Transport Survey (India), 1967 (Box 70)
    - Vols. II-IV
    - Summary and Recommendations
  - Rural Progress in Taiwan, 1960
  - Taiwan
    - Factories and products
    - Budget data (Box 71)
    - U.S. aid program
    - Agricultural developments
  - Eastern Region Transport Survey (India), 1967
    - Vol. II
    - Vol. IV, Part 1
    - Vol. V, Part 2
    - Vols. VI-VII
  - Farm Mechanization Program for Korea, 1972 (Box 72)
  - Asian language report, 1956
  - Energy Resources and National Policy, 1939
  - Calcutta Port Annual, 1970
  - Report on Kobe-Nagoya Expressway Survey, 1956
  - Evaluation of Kobe-Nagoya Expressway Survey, 1957
  - Report of the Committee for the Study of the Kobe-Nagoya Expressway Survey Report, 1957
  - Correspondence, 1953
    - A
    - B-R (Box 73)
    - S-Z (Box 74)
  - Correspondence, 1952
    - Department of the Army
    - A-M
    - N-Z (Box 75)
  - Correspondence, 1951
    - A-T
    - U-Z (Box 76)
  - Correspondence, 1950
    - Columbia University Seminar in Economic Mobilization Planning
    - A-Z
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 77)
    - Academy of Political Science
    - Associated University Bureaus of Business and Economic Research
    - Indexes of Business Sentiment
    - National Industrial Conference Board
    - A-Z
  - Correspondence, 1944-1945
  - Survey of the Domestic Transport of India's Export Cargo, Vol. I, 1971
  - Miscellany (Box 78)
  - Taiwan contract, 1961
  - Brookings Institution Korea project
  - Outline of the Second Five-Year Plan, (Pakistan), 1960-65 1960
  - Economic Development: Current Research and Problem Areas, 1958
  - Mathematics and the Social Sciences symposium, 1963
  - Consumer Credit, Economic Growth and Economic Stability
  - Social Science Research Council Committee on Analysis of Economic Census Data, 1961
  - The Role of the Federal Government in Financing Higher Education
  - Saigon budget
  - The Brookings Research Program in Governmental Studies, 1962
  - Brookings Institution economic program, 1962
  - The Act for International Development, 1961
  - The Economy of Taiwan (Box 79)
  - Biographical sketches
  - Economic Development Planning in Taiwan, 1961
  - Miscellany
  - Economic Growth in the United States, 1958
  - Metropolitan Rapid Transit Survey, 1957
  - Growth and Taxes, 1961
  - University of Hong Kong Symposium on Economic and Social Problems of the Far East, 1961
  - Tape recordings
  - Miscellany (Box 80)
  - Reform in Statutory Pay Provisions, 1962
  - Economic Progress of Free China, 1951-1958
  - Saigon, 1962
  - The Investment Background in Malawi
  - Functionalism in the Social Sciences, 1965
  - Statement on international liquidity, 1963
  - Ephemeral printed matter
  - Ephemeral printed matter (Box 81)
  - Egypt
    - Meetings
    - Menzler, Gerhard, and Qattara Depression Project, 1976
    - Migration projections
    - Models
    - Montasser, Essam
    - Petroleum Ministry
    - Pictures, 1975
    - Planning Ministry
    - Population
    - Port congestion, 1975
    - Port Said, 1975-1976
    - Projections consensus
    - Prynn, Peter, 1975
    - Suez Canal Zone Regional Plan: Preliminary Considerations on a Regional Railroad Plan, 1975
    - Regional population (Suez region), 1975 (Box 82)
    - Relationship of national accounts data
    - Saleh, Ahmad-el-Sayed
    - Sadler, Peter
    - Savings data
    - Societa Italiana per Condotti d'Acqua
    - Statistical notes
    - Status report #1, 1975
    - Regional Plan Steering Committee
    - The Development Outlook: Industry: Free Zone
    - Suez Canal Authority
    - SWECO reports - Tenth of Ramadan City
    - Mechanization of Cargo Handling in Maritime Commerce, 1975
    - Task Force on Economics and Population
    - Wengraf, R. J., memoranda
    - Arab Republic of Egypt: Recent Economic Developments, 1978
  - Miscellany (Box 83)
  - Ephemeral publications of the Brookings Institution and other organizations
  - Tax Reform in Vietnam: Immediate Measures and Basic Requirements, 1961
  - Political Development in the Emerging Countries: Challenge to United States Foreign Policy, 1961
  - Conference on Research for the Improvement of Development Assistance Programs and Questions, 1961
  - Changes in the Location of Manufacturing in the United States since 1929, Parts II-III, 1960 (Box 84)
  - Miscellany
  - The Brookings Institution Program in Economic Research, 1957
  - Egypt
    - Labor force
    - The Egyptian Industrial Sector, 1975
    - The Egyptian Economy, 1975
    - Tippetts-Abbett-McCarthy-Stratton personnel reports
    - TAMS' Role in the Ministry of Development and New Communities, 1978
    - Suez Governorate map
    - Suez demonstration project
    - Suez Canal region (Box 85)
    - Statistical equations, formulae and sources
    - Statistical accounting system
    - Which Future for Alexandria?, 1977
    - Shiakat list by governorates
    - Shadow pricing analysis by Taylor Binnie, 1977
    - Realistic Hopes, 1978
    - Sadat City, 1976
    - Regional plan population projections, 1976
    - Relocation of government agencies, 1977
    - Regional plan outline, 1976
    - Regional plan
    - Red Sea Governorate, 1977
    - Qattara Depression Project
    - Tax problem overseas
    - Laws #43 and 32, (1974) (1977)
    - Larsen-Nielsen project (manpower training)
    - Laws #62 and 113, (1974) (1975)
    - Paris Consultative Group
    - Loans of documents and books
  - London University Development Planning Unit
  - Low, Dana E.
  - Thomas W. Mackesey, 1908-1976
  - Japan visit
  - King Khalid City, Egypt (Box 86)
  - Korea farm mechanization program, 1971-1972
  - Egypt
    - Industrial plan, Suez Canal region
    - Industry, 1977
    - Inflation measures
  - The International Energy Situation: Outlook to 1985, 1977
  - Egypt
    - Iron and steel output, 1978
    - Investment and Free Zones Authority
    - Investments planned, 1977
  - Japan - Saburo Okita
  - Egypt
    - Transport Ministry - Youssef Ezzeldine
    - United Nations Development Programme - Suez Canal region projects
  - Van Fleet, James A.
  - Gaines, Tilford
  - Egypt
    - Industrial plan (Suez Canal region)
    - Governorates, Areas of, 1977 (Box 87)
    - Hansen, Bent, and Hollis Chenery
    - Helwan
    - Holidays, 1977
    - Housing
    - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development
  - International Labor Organization
  - Egypt
    - Tecneco proposal, 1977
    - Telegraph office
    - Tenth of Ramadan City, 1977
    - Tindal, William C.
  - Tokyo trip
  - Egypt
    - Toubar, Samir - Port survey
    - Tourism
  - A 265 Room Hotel Project in Taipei, 1961
  - Report of a Mission to Review Highway Transport Policy in India, 1963
  - Certain Aspects of the Indian Steel Industry, 1966
  - Transport and Energy in Economic Development, with Special Reference to India, 1965
  - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development Mission to India, 1964-65
    - Report #1, Agricultural Policy in India, Appendices 6-15
    - Report #1, Agricultural Policy in India, including Appendices 1-5 (Box 88)
    - Summary report
    - Report #6a, Problems of Public Financial Policy in India
    - Report #5, Physical Controls on Resource Allocation and Investment
    - Report #4, Some Observations on Planning, including tables and appendix
    - Report #3, Statistical Operations
    - Report #2, Export and Export Policy (Box 89)
    - Report #9, The Family Planning Program
    - Report #8, Problems in the Development of Manufacturing Industry with Special Reference to Public Sector Enterprise, including Appendices 1-4
    - Report #7, Key Issues of Transport Policy
    - Report #6b, Financial Policy in India
  - National Transportation Plan (Ecuador), 1964
  - Report of the Haldia Study Team (India), Vol. III, 1965
  - Report of the Haldia Study Team (India), Vols. I-II, 1965 (Box 90)
  - Current Economic Position and Prospects of India, 1966
  - The Performance of Government Undertakings, 1958-1965 (India), 1967
  - Jute, 1967
  - The Commercial Vehicle Industry in India
  - Top 200 Companies (India), 1964
  - Printed matter
  - Data on the Indian Economy, 1951 to 1969, 1970 (Box 91)
  - End of Tour Report (India), 1971
  - Walinsky, Louis J., memorandum (India), 1969
  - Development of the Suez Canal Regional Plan, 1976
  - Suez Canal Regional Plan, Status Reports 1-2, 1975
  - Effects of R&D on the Productivity Growth of Industries, 1974
  - A Study of Overseas Transport and Freight Structure in India's Export Trade, 1969
  - Economic and Social Costs of Modernization and Development, 1973
  - Ford Foundation Assistance to Indian Development Programs and Projects: Annual Status Report, 1969
  - Trade Wars or Trade Negotiations?, 1970
  - Printed matter
  - Suez Canal Regional Plan Working Papers (Box 92)
    - Natural Resources, Mineral Resources and Related Industries, 1976
    - The Egyptian Labour Force, 1976
    - Impact of the Regional Plan on the Construction Industry, 1976
    - Estimated Capital Requirements of the Area Plans, 1976-2000
    - Projections of Employment and Regional Domestic Product for the Area Plans, 1976
  - Development of the Suez Canal Regional Plan: Summary, 1976
  - Printed matter
  - China directory project
  - Directory addition proposal, 1973
  - Miscellany (Box 93)
  - Reflections from the Kobe-Nagoya Expressway Survey Seventeen Years Later, 1973
  - Takeda, Fumio
  - Transportation and National Policy, 1942
  - China
  - Addresses (Box 94)
  - Miscellany
  - Japan-Korea trip, 1952
  - Correspondence, 1956
  - North Africa, 1943-1944
  - Tape recorded interview, 1952
  - Statistical Outline of India, 1970